[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
I joined Prudential life insurance gonna
limited two years ago
it was at the peak of the coveted
pandemic and everyone was not sure what
the new normal will be
my career with Prudential was not my
first job I had a career in banking
previously
I heard about the career through a
French and former supervisor she walked
me through the career
and the career path and the various
benefits of a career with Prudential
I then joined a virtual business
opportunity presentation due to the
pandemic discussed the move with my
family and made that call to join
Prudential what's the career with
Prudential offered me was an opportunity
I had not yet experienced
unlimited earnings ownership in the
planning of my time and even more
presently more quality time with family
and friends
after six months of joining Prudential I
was awarded the best rookie agent and
most promising agent for 2020 during the
gala August Night in December held at
the LA Palm Royal Beach Hotel
in just a year and four months on the
job I have become a team leader and
qualified for Prudential Diamond Club
in fact I was in turkey and Dubai as a
member of the diamond club and such a
wonderful experience from shopping in
Istanbul to the watermarks in Dubai all
reward and recognition of my hard work I
have also qualified for the Million
Dollar Round Table mblt the world's most
prestigious recognition of professional
Life Insurance Financial Consultants I
achieved this by doing a minimum of
three appointments daily
actively acting for referrals and being
referable and finally building a lasting
relationship with my clients
for that need career professional and
sure and looking for a rewarding new
challenge a career with credential is
your best choice
if you are bent out not too sure of your
progress or if your effort and
recognition is not to recognize where
you are or you are looking to increase
your earnings take a look at me and my
journey in just two years I can assure
you that Journey Prudential will be one
of your best decisions for you and your
loved ones thank you
[Music]